We're a data consulting company as we do about 500K.
I'd like to get the 1.2 million.
Our biggest issue is leads, leads and leads.
How do you charge?
Hourly.
Hourly?
Yes.
Oh, oh, oh dear me.
Let's just get you to 1.2 million
and get you no more customers
and just change how you bill.
How about that?
Let me give you a really sexy thing.
I want you to give five one-on-one calls away for free
as the offer.
Now there's an asterisk there
that it's only for companies that meet your criteria.
I think your offer needs to be around the ROI
and you need to use something called a calculator close.
So if you say, hey, I'm gonna save you 200 grand.
I charge 30% of what I save.
So it's 60.
That way you're charging for outcomes, not hours.
The big step here is that we wanna take those calls
to talk about what is going to happen,
not how to do what is going to happen.
It all works.
All you have to do is set the frame
at the beginning of this.
It's like, hey, to be clear, are you good with me?
Walk through these five calls at the end of the fifth call.
I'll explain kinda how what working with us might look like.
In the meantime, I wanna just provide you a lot of value.
Yes, yes.
Right, exactly.
We're gonna describe it, not explain it.